bloggingfusion.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy Blogging Fusion - Blog Directory - Article Directory - RSS Directory - Web Directory

## Privacy Policy Policy

When you provide us with information through this website, we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Your visit to this website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. 

Information Collection and How it is used

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us upon submission and inclusion within our blog directory which the site is intended for. For example, if Blogging Fusion decides to require a user registration in order to submit your websites details, you will be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, location), and information about your website/blog. 

Blogging Fusion services does collect the following information about your website upon receiving your website submission through third party services, such as Alexa™ Traffic Report, Google® Page Rank Algorithm, Yahoo™ and MSN®. We are not responsible for the accuracy of the data collected by third party vendors. 

To protect your personal information, users registering for these services will be given a unique username, password and unique blog or registration ID which should be refrenced when corresponding to staff or editors of this blog directory. Subject to your consent, the information you provide may be used by us to communicate new features, information related to the blog directory or special promotions and features being added that may be of intrest to you. 

We will never send unsolicited email or spam. This is strictly against our terms of services and is why your email address is never published publicly to protect you from unwanted solicitation. 

We may also use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use or interation of this website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular how frequent the stay and what intrestes most visitors have regarding our website. 

We may disclose any information we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental agency upon request. 

If you would prefer that we do not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any by not participating in our website. 

Cookies and Log Files

We may place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user, recall your preferences and personalize your experience. A cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track your use of our website and remember your preferences. The cookie will be stored on your computer's hard drive until you remove it. You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookie, you may still use our Website, but you may be limited in the use of some of the functions and features. 

In addition, we may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our website, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate office use only. 

Third Parties Affilation

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf in relation to the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. Examples include data analysis firms like Google Anayltics™, customer support agents, directory editors and web hosting companies. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

Google Anayltics™

Blogging Fusion Blog Directory pages may contain Google Analytics™ code, sometimes called web statistics that allow us to count users who have visited certain pages. Blogging Fusion Blog Directory may use web statistics in conjunction with: promotional e-mail messages, online advertising or newsletters. This is done solely to determine the effectiveness of these activities. Web statistics collect a limited set of information including a Cookie (see above section on Cookies), which identifies the referring source, pages viewed and the time of access. Web statistics are not used to access your personal information on Blogging Fusion Blog Directory in any way. Web statistics information is not stored or transmitted to any third party at any time. 

Third Party Links

This website contains links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our website or otherwise visit. 

Security

We have implemented various security measures to protect the security of your personal information, both on line and off line. If you have any questions about the security of our Website, you can contact us using the following form. 

Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our directory, we sell or add features for sponsor listings. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on the website you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances. 

Our website uses a thrid party merchant 'Paypal™,' to handle all buisness transactions or purchases. This Privacy Policy does not cover the association with Paypal™, so you are advised to read their Privacy Policy to understand how they collect and use your personal information. 

Paypal™ [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). 

Notification of Changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. 

Please note that our rights to use your personal identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time of the use. If the preceding sentence is deemed to violate applicable law, the privacy policy in effect at the time your personal identifiable information was collected will apply. 

Updating Your Information

You may make changes to your personally identifiable information by e-mailing us using the following contact form. You also may request that we remove your personal identifiable information from our databases by e-mailing us using the following contact form. 

Choice/Opt-Out

When you register at this website, you may opt-out of receiving future communications from us at anytime. You may change your preferences at any time by revising your profile or, if you do not have a profile, by emailing us using the following contact form. 

Data Holder

The information you provide to use will be managed by the Director of Blogging Fusion Blog Directory, PO BOX 22121, Belleville, Ontario Canada. K8N5V7 

Comments

We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit at Blogging Fusion Blog Directory is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please email us using the following contact form. 

Privacy Policy 01/02/2007 © Blogging Fusion Blog Directory
